Guide to the Frank Lyon Polk Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1898-(1915-1920)-1942; Series I; 6.5 linear feet (16 boxes)
  - Moltke, Carl Poul Oscar
    See: Constantin Brun (1919 May 30), box 3, folder 86
  - Moore, John Bassett, 1916 February March, 1918 March - April (Box 10, Folder 359)
  - Moore, Robert Walton, 1935 May - June (Box 10, Folder 359)
  - Moores, Merrill, 1916 May (Box 10, Folder 360)
  - Morgan, E[dwin?] D., 1916 July (Box 10, Folder 360)
  - Morgan, Edwin Vernon, 1919 March - April (Box 10, Folder 360)
    See also: Brazil, box 23, folder 166
  - Morgan, Henry H., 1916 Nov, 1917 January (Box 10, Folder 361)
  - Morgan, Marshall
    See: Mexico, box 29, folder 455
  - Morgan (J. P.) and Co.
    See: Martin Egan (1915-1917), box 5, folders 161-162 See: Mexico, box 29, folder 492 See: Miscellaneous, box 30, folder 521
  - Morgenthau, Henry, 1920 April - May, 1921 September (Box 10, Folder 362)
    See also: Woodrow Wilson (1917 Jul 12), box 14, folder 496 See also: Poland, box 32, folder 622
  - Morris, Ira Nelson, 1918 March - April (Box 10, Folder 362)
  - Morrison, Frank
  - Morrow, Dwight W.
    See: Miscellaneous, box 30, folder 521
  - Morse, Perley, 1917 April (Box 10, Folder 362)
  - Moses, George H., 1919 April - May (Box 10, Folder 363)
  - Moskowitz, Henry
    See:, box 3, folder 105
  - Mullins, Thomas Darragh, 1919 July (Box 10, Folder 363)
  - Munson, Frank C., 1917 December (Box 10, Folder 363)
  - Murray, Arthur Cecil, 1936 Feb, 1939 December (Box 10, Folder 364)
  - Murray, Robert Hammond, 1917 Dec, 1919 June - July (Box 10, Folder 364)
    See also: Norman Hapgood (1916 Sep 30), box 7, folder 231 See: Mexico, box 29, folder 452
  - Nansen, Fridtjof, 1918 May (Box 10, Folder 365)
  - Narodny, Ivan I., 1917 July - August (Box 10, Folder 365)
  - Nast, Condé
  - National Association of Clothiers, 1916 January (Box 10, Folder 365)
  - National Conference for Continuous Mediation
    See: Peace Efforts, box 32, folder 595
  - National Oil and Development Company
    See: Mexico, box 30, folder 504
  - National Polish Committee of America, 1920 January (Box 10, Folder 365)
  - National Zinc Company
  - Navarro, Alfonso de, 1913 Apr, 1917 July (Box 10, Folder 366)
  - (*) Neale, S. C., 1916 July - 1917 February (Box 10, Folder 366)
  - Nevill, Richard, 1918 February (Box 10, Folder 366)
  - New York (City), Department of Licenses
    See: George H. Bell, box 2, folder 45
  - New York (City), Fire Department
    See: Robert Adamson, box 1, folder 2
  - New York County Lawyers' Association, 1926 June (Box 10, Folder 366)
  - New York Evening Post, 1916 November (Box 10, Folder 367)
  - New York Public Library, 1921 December (Box 10, Folder 367)
  - New York Times, 1917 April - May; 1919 Jul; 1928 May, November (Box 10, Folder 367)
  - New York World
    See: Charles M. Lincoln, box 9, folder 327
  - Newton, Byron R., 1917 Oct, 1918 Dec, 1919 June, 1920 June (Box 10, Folder 368)
  - Niblack, A. P.
    See: Adriatic Question, box 21, folder 3
  - Nicholson, George P., 1923 January (Box 10, Folder 368)
  - Nielsen, Fred Kenelm
    See: American Mission, box 22, folder 99 See: Mexico, box 29, folder 471
  - Nieman, Lucius W., 1917 Jun, November (Box 10, Folder 368)
  - Niles-Noble (Box 10, Folder 369)
    - Niles Bement-Pond Company, 1917 July (Box 10, Folder 369)
    - Nipgen, Alvin T., 1917 June (Box 10, Folder 369)
    - Noble, Herbert, 1917 April (Box 10, Folder 369)
  - Nordvall, A. R., 1917 July - August (Box 10, Folder 370)
  - Noyes, Frank B., 1917 August (Box 10, Folder 370)
  - Noyes, Pierrepont B., 1919 Aug, Oct; 1921 February (Box 10, Folder 370)
  - Nye, J. M., 1918 Aug, 1919 Jun, [1920 pre-Apr?], undated (Box 10, Folder 370)
  - O'Brian-O'Keeffe (Box 10, Folder 371)
    - O'Brian, John Lord, 1918 Mar, October (Box 10, Folder 371)
    - O'Brien, John F., 1917 February (Box 10, Folder 371)
    - O'Ceallaigh, Seán Z., 1919 October - November (Box 10, Folder 371)
    - O'Keeffe, Arthur J., 1915 Sep, 1919 Apr, 1924 July (Box 10, Folder 371)
  - Oldfield, William A.
  - Olivier, M., 1939 June (Box 10, Folder 372)
  - Olney, Richard (1871-1939), 1915 Dec, 1916 Nov, 1920 Feb, 1924 July (Box 10, Folder 372)
  - Osborne, D. G., 1917 October (Box 10, Folder 372)
  - O'Sullivan, Charles, 1927 August (Box 11, Folder 373)
  - Oudin, Maurice Angus, 1917 Aug, November (Box 11, Folder 373)
  - Oviatt, Edwin, 1918 October (Box 11, Folder 373)
  - Owens, Clarence J.
    See: Belisario Porras, box 11, folder 405
  - Paderewski, Ignacy Jan, 1919 October (Box 11, Folder 374)
  - Paderewski Fund for Poland, 1921 February (Box 11, Folder 374)
  - Page, Alice (Mrs. Walter Hines), 1918 December (Box 11, Folder 374)
  - Page, Thomas Nelson, 1918 Feb, Jul, September (Box 11, Folder 374)
  - Page, Walter Hines, 1915 September - Oct; 1916 June - Jul, September - Dec; 1917 January - Dec; 1918 March (Box 11, Folder 375-381)
  - Paine, Ralph D., 1915 Sep, [1918 Mar?] (Box 11, Folder 382)
  - (*) Palmer, Alexander Mitchell, 1918 January - 1919 April (Box 11, Folder 382)
  - Palmer, Bradley W., 1918 January - 1919 March (Box 11, Folder 383)
  - Palmer, Eric H.
    See: Edwin Björkman, box 2, folder 54
  - Palmer, Frederick, 1917 December (Box 11, Folder 383)
  - Pan American Union, 1917 Jul, 1919 February (Box 11, Folder 383)
    See also: John Barrett, box 2, folder 40
  - Pan American Wireless Telephone and Telegraph Company
    See: Latin America, box 28, folders 421-422
  - Panateroff, Stephan, 1916 October - 1917 Dec, 1919 June (Box 11, Folder 384)
  - Pan-Epirotic Union in America
  - Parker, James S., 1917 October (Box 11, Folder 384)
  - Parker, Louis A., 1919 September - October (Box 11, Folder 384)
  - Parker, Myron M.
    See: Mexico, box 29, folder 488
  - Parsons, William Barclay, 1922 March (Box 11, Folder 385)
  - Patchin, Philip H., 1918 Dec, 1919 May, 1928 November (Box 11, Folder 385)
  - Patrick, Mary Mills, 1919 July (Box 11, Folder 385)
  - Patten, Mary, 1919 July (Box 11, Folder 386)
  - Patterson, A. M., 1920 May (Box 11, Folder 386)
  - Patterson, William Morrison, 1918 November (Box 11, Folder 386)
  - Peabody, Endicott, 1910 September; 1911 September; 1914 Jan; 1915 September; 1923 Mar; 1927 Feb; 1933 May, September (Box 11, Folder 387)
  - Pelham, Thomas W., 1917 August (Box 11, Folder 387)
  - Peoples Industrial Trading Corporation
    See: Poland, box 32, folder 633
  - Percy, Eustace, 1917 May - October (Box 11, Folder 387)
  - Pergler, Charles, 1918 February - March (Box 11, Folder 388)
  - Perkins, Thomas Nelson, 1917 Jun, 1918 January (Box 11, Folder 388)
  - Perkins, Wallace T., 1923 March (Box 11, Folder 388)
  - Pershing, John J., 1919 August (Box 11, Folder 389)
  - Pesqueira, Roberto V.
    See: Charles A. Douglas, box 5, folder 151
  - Pétain, Philippe, 1939 May (Box 11, Folder 389)
  - Pezet, Federico Alfonso, 1920 September (Box 11, Folder 389)
  - Phelan, James D.
    See: Franklin K. Lane (1919 May 2), box 8, folder 298 See: Ireland, box 27, folder 370 See: Japan, box 28, folder 400
  - (*) Phelps Brothers and Company, 1917 June - 1918 September (Box 11, Folder 390-392)
  - Philip, Hoffman, 1919 February - 1920 January (Box 11, Folder 393)
  - Philipot, ____, 1919 August (Box 11, Folder 393)
  - Philipsen, V. O. J.
    See: Denmark, box 24, folder 227 See: Russia, box 33, folder 707
  - Phillips, William
    - (*), 1916 Jan, April - July 13 (Box 11, Folder 394)
      See also: Mexico, box 29, folder 457
    - (*), 1916 July [15?] - November (Box 11, Folder 395)
      See also: Mexico, box 29, folder 468
    - (*), 1917 February - Oct; 1918 January - Apr, August - December (Box 11, Folder 396-397)
    - (*), 1919 June - September 18 (Box 11, Folder 398)
      See also: William E. Gonzales (1919 Jul 1), box 6, folder 214
    - 1919 September 26 - November (Box 11, Folder 399)
    - (*), 1920 February - Dec, 1925 Dec, 1927 Nov, 1933 Mar, 1940 Jul, 1941 Apr, undated (Box 11, Folder 400)
  - Pichon, Stéphen Marie, 1919 December (Box 11, Folder 401)
  - Piez, Charles
    See: Labor, box 28, folder 411
  - Pittman, Key, 1915 December - 1916 January (Box 11, Folder 401)
  - Polish National Committee
    See: Poland, box 32, folder 617
  - Polk, Beach, 1917 September (Box 11, Folder 402)
  - Polk, Elizabeth Sturgis ("Lily"), 1916 Aug, undated (Box 11, Folder 402)
  - (*) Polk, Ida Ashe (Lyon) (Mrs. William Mecklenburg), 1898 May - Sep, undated (Box 11, Folder 403)
  - Polk, J. Metcalfe, undated (Box 11, Folder 404)
  - Polk, John Metcalf ("Jack"), 1916 Jul, undated (Box 11, Folder 404)
  - Polk, William Mecklenburg
    See: Ida Ashe (Lyon) Polk (Mrs. William M.), box 11, folder 403
  - Porras, Belisario, 1919 March - June (Box 11, Folder 405)
  - Porras, M. F.
    See: F. A. Pezet, box 11, folder 389
  - Porter, Howard, 1919 December (Box 11, Folder 405)
  - Postal Telegraph-Cable Company
  - Potter, Howard, 1916 March (Box 11, Folder 406)
  - Potter, James, 1920 February (Box 11, Folder 406)
  - Potter, James Brown, 1917 December (Box 11, Folder 406)
  - Potter, Robert S., 1917 May (Box 11, Folder 406)
  - Pottle, Emery, 1919 September - October (Box 11, Folder 407)
  - Pou, Edward W., 1917 September (Box 11, Folder 407)
  - [Poublitoff, S.?], [post-1917 Oct?] (Box 11, Folder 407)
  - Pratt, Edward Ewing, 1916 January (Box 11, Folder 408)
  - Pratt, William Veazie, [1918 post-Oct?], 1929 July (Box 11, Folder 408)
  - Price, Jesse D., 1916 July (Box 11, Folder 408)
  - Price, Joseph M.
    See: Norman Hapgood (1916 Feb 7), box 7, folder 231
  - Price, William W., 1902 Dec, 1914 May, 1919 Dec, 1921 Mar, undated (Box 12, Folder 409)
  - Proctor, Frank C.
  - Proskey, W. Scott, 1917 April - May (Box 12, Folder 409)
  - Providence Journal
    See: Woodrow Wilson (1916 Mar 16), box 14, folder 490
  - Provisional Executive Committee for General Zionist Affairs
  - Public Ledger (Philadelphia)
    See: Herbert Bruce Brougham, box 3, folder 75
  - Pyne, Percy R., 1919 June - July (Box 12, Folder 409)
  - Quattrone, Francesco, 1918 July (Box 12, Folder 410)
  - Quinn, John, 1917 March (Box 12, Folder 410)
  - Quintana, Frederico M., 1915 March (Box 12, Folder 410)
  - Ragsdale, J. Willard, 1917 July (Box 12, Folder 411)
  - Randolph, Harrison, 1920 Feb, 1924 January (Box 12, Folder 411)
  - Ransdell, Joseph E., 1921 January (Box 12, Folder 412)
  - Rappaport, Leo M.
    See: Merrill Moores, box 10, folder 360
  - Rappard, W. L. F. C. van, 1916 June - Dec, 1917 Aug, 1918 March (Box 12, Folder 412)
  - Rasquin, William, Jr., 1916 May (Box 12, Folder 413)
  - Rattigan, William F. A.
    See: Rumania, box 32, folder 655
  - Rea, George Bronson, 1920 January - February (Box 12, Folder 413)
  - Reading, Alice (Mrs. Rufus Daniel Isaacs), 1918 June (Box 12, Folder 414)
  - (*) Reading, Rufus Daniel Isaacs, 1st marquis of Reading, 1918 January - Jul, 1919 June
  - (*) Redfield, William C., 1916 Feb, July, Nov; 1917 June - Oct; 1918 Feb, July, Dec; 1919 January - July (Box 12, Folder 415-416)
  - Reed, James Alexander, 1918 December (Box 12, Folder 417)
    See also: France, box 25, folder 257
  - Reinsch, Paul S., 1918 December - 1919 April (Box 12, Folder 417)
  - Requa, Mark Lawrence
    See: Mexico, box 29, folder 477
  - Réquin, Édouard Jean, 1918 Feb, October (Box 12, Folder 417)
  - (*) Riano y Gayangos, Don Juan, 1916 March - Aug, 1917 July - Aug, 1918 May - Nov, 1926 July (Box 12, Folder 418)
  - Rice, Cecil Arthur Spring
    See: Spring Rice, Cecil Arthur, box 12, folders 441-444
  - Richards, Eben
  - Richardson, W. P.
    See: Russia, box 33, folder 696
  - Riker, Carroll Livingston, 1915 November (Box 12, Folder 419)
  - Riker, Samuel, Jr., 1917 August (Box 12, Folder 419)
  - Rintelen, Franz von
    See: Charles Warren (1917 May 5), box 13, folder 474
  - Robbins, Herbert D., 1918 March (Box 12, Folder 419)
  - Robbins, Warren D.
    See: Cuba, box 24, folder 208
  - Robertson, Randolph, 1917 March - Apr, Sep; 1920 June (Box 12, Folder 420)
  - Robinson, Joe T., 1916 Apr, 1919 July (Box 12, Folder 420)
  - Roessler and Hasslacher Chemical Company
    See: Key Pittman, box 11, folder 401
  - Rogers, Walter S., 1917 October (Box 12, Folder 420)
  - Romanos, A., 1919 September (Box 12, Folder 421)
  - (*) Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1913 May, 1915 November - Dec, 1917 May, 1919 May - Jul, 1920 Jul, undated (Box 12, Folder 421)
    See also: Walter Hines Page (1917 Jan 25), box 11, folders 379
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, Jr., 1932 February (Box 12, Folder 421)
  - Root, Elihu, 1919 March - April (Box 12, Folder 422)
    See also: Samuel Reading Bertron (1919 Mar 20-24), box 2, folder 49
  - Root, Elihu, Jr., 1920 April (Box 12, Folder 422)
  - Rosen, Roman
    See: Russia, box 33, folder 684
  - Rosenthal, Moritz
    See: Alien Property Custodian, box 22, folder 95
  - Ross, E. P.
    See: Denmark, box 24, folder 227
  - Rowe, Leo S., 1915 Sep, 1917 March - Jul, 1919 Jun, 1920 March - December (Box 12, Folder 422)
    See also: Bolivia, box 23, folder 161 See also: Mexico, box 29, folder 469 See also: Venezuela, box 36, folder 845
  - Rowe, William W., 1916 October (Box 12, Folder 423)
  - Ruddock, Albert Billings
    See: Adriatic Question, box 22, folder 75
  - Rush, Thomas E., 1910 Nov, 1924 July (Box 12, Folder 423)
  - Russian-American-Asiatic Corporation
    See: Ivan I. Narodny, box 10, folder 365
  - Ryan, Edward W., 1919 Oct, 1920 [post-March 1] - June (Box 12, Folder 423)
  - Sabin, Charles Hamilton, 1919 May (Box 12, Folder 424)
  - Sabin, Paulette Morton (Mrs. Charles Hamilton), 1924 July (Box 12, Folder 424)
  - Saint Cyr, A. de, 1919 February (Box 12, Folder 424)
  - Salmon, David Alden, 1919 January (Box 12, Folder 425)
  - Sanford, Ethel, 1922 May (Box 12, Folder 425)
  - Sartiges, Etienne Gilbert Eugène, comte de, 1926 June (Box 12, Folder 425)
  - Saxe, John Godfrey, 1918 Dec, 1920 September (Box 12, Folder 426)
  - Sazonov, Sergei
    See: Poland, box 32, folder 629
  - Schelling, Ernest H., 1917 December - 1918 November (Box 12, Folder 426)
  - Scherbatskoy, A., 1921 June (Box 12, Folder 426)
  - Schiff, Jacob
    See: Japan, box 28, folder 394
  - Schoenfeld, Hans F. A.
    See: Rumania, box 32, folder 650
  - Scholle, Gustave, 1917 November (Box 12, Folder 427)
  - Schurman, Jacob Gould, 1915 October (Box 12, Folder 427)
  - Schurz, Carl L., 1917 April (Box 12, Folder 427)
  - Scott, Edgar, 1917 May (Box 12, Folder 428)
  - Scott, James B.
    See: Aerial Navigation Convention, box 22, folders 87-88) See: American Mission, box 22, folder 99\ See: Austria, box 22, folder 132 See: German Tankers, box 25, folder 275 See: Germany, box 25, folder 297
  - Scully, P. J., 1919 April (Box 12, Folder 428)
  - Secor, Alson
    See: David F. Houston, box 8, folder 275
  - Selden, Charles A., 1919 Sep, undated (Box 12, Folder 428)
  - Serbian Press Bureau, 1918 July (Box 12, Folder 429)
  - Seskis, Jânis, 1919 September (Box 12, Folder 429)
  - Seymour, Charles, 1925 November (Box 12, Folder 429)
  - Sharp, William G., 1917 December (Box 12, Folder 429)
  - Shaw, Gardiner Howland
    - 1919 Jul, 1920 June - September, 1921 March - September (Box 12, Folder 430)
      See also: Greece, box 26, folder 340
      See also: Mexico, box 29, folders 496-497
    - (*) 1922 Mar; 1924 May - Jun; 1925 Mar; 1928 Mar, Dec; 1941 October (Box 12, Folder 431)
  - Sheffield, James R., 1914 January (Box 12, Folder 432)
    See also: Finland, box 25, folder 245
  - Sheldon, Edward Wright, 1926 June (Box 12, Folder 432)
  - Shepardson, Whitney, 1919 June - November (Box 12, Folder 432)
  - Sheppard, Morris, 1915 Nov, 1916 Aug, 1917 February (Box 12, Folder 433)
  - Sherley, Swagar, 1915 Nov; 1916 Jul, Nov; 1918 February - April (Box 12, Folder 433)
  - Sherman, [Merritt Masters?], 1918 April (Box 12, Folder 434)
  - Shipley, Ruth, [1922 Jul?] (Box 12, Folder 434)
  - Short, Camilla, undated (Box 12, Folder 434)
  - Sibbet, H. A., 1916 June (Box 12, Folder 435)
  - Simon, Joseph, 1918 March - April (Box 12, Folder 435)
  - Skiddy, W. W., 1915 Dec, 1916 April (Box 12, Folder 435)
  - Skinner, Robert P., 1915 November - 1916 May (Box 12, Folder 436)
  - Slayden, James Luther
    See: Great Britain, box 26, folder 319
  - Smith, Alfred E., 1918 Sep, 1920 Nov, 1928 February (Box 12, Folder 437)
  - Smith, Augustine J., 1917 April (Box 12, Folder 437)
  - Smith, Edward N., 1915 October (Box 12, Folder 437)
  - Smith, Hoke, 1918 Jun, 1921 January (Box 12, Folder 438)
  - Smith, Ulysses Grant, 1919 April (Box 12, Folder 438)
  - Smith-Gordon, Lionel
    See: Duncan Upshaw Fletcher, box 5, folder 177
  - Society of the Friends of Music
    See: Harriet A. B. Lanier, box 8, folder 299
  - Sokolow, Nahum, 1919 October (Box 12, Folder 438)
  - Sol M, Salvador, 1920 June (Box 12, Folder 439)
  - Sonneborn (L.) Sons, Inc., 1917 May (Box 12, Folder 439)
  - "Sookine," ____
    See: William Phillips (1917 Oct 30), box 11, folders 396
  - Soulié, Henry, 1919 August (Box 12, Folder 440)
  - Spanish Red Cross
    See: American Red Cross, box 1, folder 5
  - Spencer, Nelson S.
  - Speyer and Co., 1915 Sep, 1916 October
    See also: Chandler P. Anderson (1916 May - Dec), box 1, folder 6
  - Spring Rice, Cecil Arthur
    - (*), 1915 December - 1916 February (Box 12, Folder 441)
      See also: Japan, box 28, folder 386
    - (*), 1916 March - Oct, 1917 March - July (Box 12, Folder 442-443)
    - (*), 1917 August - 1918 Feb, undated (Box 12, Folder 444)
      See also: Richard Crawford (1917 Aug 24), box 4, folder 126
      See also: Russia, box 33, folder 670
  - Spring-Rice, Florence (Mrs. Cecil Arthur), 1918 December - 1919 January (Box 12, Folder 445)
  - Stabler, Jordan Herbert, 1919 March - Apr, 1925 December, undated (Box 12, Folder 445)
    See also: Argentina, box 22, folder 110 See also: Bolivia, box 23, folder 158 See also: Brazil, box 23, folder 165 See also: Columbia, box 24, folders 203-204 See also: Cuba, box 24, folder 208 See also: Ecuador, box 24, folder 232 See also: Guatemala, box 26, folder 350 See also: [Haiti?], box 26, folder 353 See also: Latin America, box 28, folders 419-422 See also: Panama, box 31, folder 581 See also: Panama, box 31, folder 583 See also: Peru, box 32, folder 610
  - Stallforth, F., 1916 March - April (Box 12, Folder 446)
  - Stamford, Mfg. Co.
    See: W. W. Skiddy, box 12, folder 435
  - Stanchfield, John B., 1917 December - 1918 March (Box 12, Folder 446)
  - Stancill, R. L., 1919 February (Box 12, Folder 446)
  - Starr Hunt, J. B.
  - Stedman, Charles M., 1915 December (Box 12, Folder 447)
  - Stefánik, C. A. S.
    See: Edouard de Billy, box 2, folder 52-53
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    See: Norman Hapgood (1916 Jan 26), box 7, folder 231 See: Russia, box 33, folder 690
  - Stevens, Guy, 1919 August (Box 12, Folder 447)
  - Stewart, William A. W., 1917 December - 1918 November (Box 12, Folder 447)
  - Stillman, James A., 1919 December (Box 12, Folder 448)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1916 December - 1917 January (Box 12, Folder 448)
  - Stokes, James Graham Phelps, 1915 November (Box 12, Folder 448)
  - Stone-Stone (Box 12, Folder 449)
    - Stone, Harlan Fiske, 1924 April (Box 12, Folder 449)
    - Stone, Melville Elijah, Jr., 1915 Nov, 1918 January (Box 12, Folder 449)
      See also: Associated Press, box 1, folder 13
    - Stone, William Joel, 1917 July (Box 12, Folder 449)
      See also: Ireland, box 27, folder 370
  - Stovall, Pleasant Alexander, 1916 Nov, 1919 Aug, 1920 June (Box 13, Folder 450)
    See also: Switzerland, box 35, folders 780-781
  - Straight, Willard Dickerman, 1916 Dec, 1917 March (Box 13, Folder 450)
  - Straus, Oscar Solomon
    See: David Rowland Francis (1916 Aug 30), box 6, folder 189
  - Strauss, Albert, 1917 November - December (Box 13, Folder 451)
  - Strong, Benjamin, 1919 September (Box 13, Folder 451)
  - Suazo, Luis, 1919 August - September (Box 13, Folder 451)
  - Sulzberger and Sons Company
    See: Lloyd C. Griscom, box 7, folder 221
  - Survey, The
    See: Paul U. Kellogg, box 8, folder 290
  - Swanson, Claude Augustus, 1919 June (Box 13, Folder 452)
  - Sweetser, Arthur, 1920 March (Box 13, Folder 452)
  - Swing, Raymond Gram, 1917 October (Box 13, Folder 452)
  - Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1916 Aug; 1918 Mar, Nov; 1920 May, July (Box 13, Folder 453)
  - Tanis, Richard C.
    See: Mexico, box 29, folder 476
  - (*) Tardieu, André Pierre Gabriel Amédée, 1917 Jun, 1918 January - Jun, 1919 Nov, 1921 March (Box 13, Folder 453)
    See also: Ellis Loring Dresel (1919 Oct 18), box 5, folder 153 See also: Adriatic Question, box 22, folder 81
  - Tarnowski, ____, 1917 Feb, May (Box 13, Folder 454)
  - Taylor, Alonzo E.
    See: Russia, box 33, folder 692
  - Taylor, Howard, 1916 June - Jul, 1919 March (Box 13, Folder 454)
    See also: Peace Efforts, box 32, folders 592-593
  - Texas Company
  - Thayer, Henry C., 1917 November (Box 13, Folder 454)
  - [Thompson, William Boyce?]
    See: Russia, box 33, folder 668 See: Russia, box 33, folder 673
  - Thorne, Samuel, Jr., 1917 Dec, 1919 May (Box 13, Folder 455)
  - Times (London)
    See: Henry M. Hall, box 7, folder 227
  - Tisza, István
  - Tittoni, Tommaso, 1919 October - November (Box 13, Folder 455)
  - Toomer, W. M., 1917 May (Box 13, Folder 456)
  - Totten, Ralph James, 1919 September - October (Box 13, Folder 456)
  - Travers, Grace Brunner
    See: Fred Hoey, box 8, folder 260
  - Trone, S. A.
    See: Thomas N. Perkins, box 11, folder 388
  - Trowbridge, S. B. P., 1917 December (Box 13, Folder 456)
  - (*) Tumulty, Joseph Patrick, 1917 Jul, December; 1919 January - Jul, December (Box 13, Folder 457)
    See also: Henry H. Childers, box 3, folder 104 See also: Martin H. Glynn, box 6, folder 209 See also: Ivan I. Narodny, box 10, folder 365 See also: Brazil, box 23, folder 166 See also: China, box 24, folder 195 See also: Ireland, box 27, folder 370 See also: Mexico, box 29, folder 456
  - (*) Tumulty, Joseph Patrick, 1920 Mar, May; 1924 July (Box 13, Folder 458)
  - Tyler, Royall
    See: Australia, box 22, folder 134 See: Australia, box 22, folder 137
  - Underwood, Oscar W., 1919 July (Box 13, Folder 459)
  - United States Fuel Administration, 1918 Apr, Oct; 1919 May - June (Box 13, Folder 459)
  - Unschuld, Marie von, 1919 July (Box 13, Folder 459)
  - Untermyer, Samuel
    See: Wenceslao de la Guardia, box 7, folder 222
  - Urueta, Carlos Adolfo, 1920 June - 1921 October (Box 13, Folder 460)
  - Vaida-Voevod, Alexandru, 1919 September - October (Box 13, Folder 461)
  - Vanderbilt, Cornelius, 1916 Jul, 1918 Jun, 1919 Aug, undated (Box 13, Folder 461)
  - Vanderlip, Frank Arthur
  - Van Dyke, Henry, 1916 February - September (Box 13, Folder 461)
  - Van Norman, Louis Edwin, 1919 January (Box 13, Folder 462)
  - Van Slyke, Warren C., 1919 March (Box 13, Folder 462)
  - Venizelos, Eleutherios K., 1919 August - Nov, 1921 October (Box 13, Folder 462)
  - [Verdeny?], Marion G., 1918 May (Box 13, Folder 463)
  - Vesnitch, Milenko R., 1919 August - Dec, 1920 August (Box 13, Folder 463)
  - Viviani, René R., 1919 September (Box 13, Folder 463)
  - Vogelstein, Ludwig, 1916 December (Box 13, Folder 464)
  - Volunteers for Peace
    See: Charles L. Bernheimer, box 2, folder 47
  - Vopicka, Charles J., 1919 October - November (Box 13, Folder 464)
  - Voûte, Emile W., 1925 January (Box 13, Folder 464)
  - Vulcan Steel Products Company, 1917 August (Box 13, Folder 464)
  - Wadhams, William H.
    See: Frederic R. Coudert (1918 Mar 23), box 4, folder 120
  - Wadsworth, James W., 1920 June (Box 13, Folder 465)
  - Wagner, R. G., 1917 February - March (Box 13, Folder 465)
  - Wales, Henry George, 1920 December (Box 13, Folder 465)
    See also: Laurence Hills, box 8, folder 258
  - Walker, Harold, 1917 April - May (Box 13, Folder 466)